# FRANK PARMAR

Unit-1511, 701 Don Mills Road, Toronto, Ontario. M3C1R7 · (647) 778 8841 Parmarfrank444@gmail.com · www.github.com/FrankParmar · www.linkedin.com/in/frankparmar

Magnificent team player and programming expert with profound knowledge of development tools and languages. Hopeful for the position of Full Stack Developer at Altus Group and have hands on experience to developing designs, coding and testing; debugging programs and adding value to business.

### **SKILLS**

- Worked on several projects.
- Proficient in .Net Framework, Python, Perl, JavaScript, Java, CSS, HTML, SQL Server, NoSQL, SQL, Swagger, AWS.
- Familiar with NodeJS, MongoDB, Nodemon, GitKraken, Anaconda.
- Positive attitude, enthusiastic with strong work ethics and a team player
- Optimistic approach, attentive listening.
- ➤ Willing to work in a dynamic, challenging and growth-oriented environment.
- Excellent problem solver.
- Good communication skills.

## **EDUCATION**

### **SOFTWARE ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGY, CENTENNIAL COLLEGE**

**SEPTEMBER 2017- MAY 2019** 

941 PROGRESS AVE, SCARBOROUGH, ONTARIO.

- Prepare a food ordering API with swagger for using CRUD technologies and RESTful API And published it using AWS (Elastic Beanstalks).
- Inventory Management System using .NET Framework and SQL Server.
- Car Parking Web Application using Java and NoSQL.
- Library Management System Database using SQL.
- Designed a 2D game in Unity just like Star Wars.

### **BACHELOR'S DEGREE, GUJARAT TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY**

**SEPTEMBER 2012- MAY 2016** 

GANDHINAGAR, GUJARAT, INDIA.

- ➤ Biometric Employee Attendance System Using SQL Server and .NET Framework.
- Hospital Management System using Java Technologies.
- Photo editing application using Android Studio.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **CASHIER, CIRCLE K**

# SEPTEMBER 07, 2017- PRESENT 4696 YOUNGE-STREET, TORONTO, ONTARIO.

- Operated: cashier and pump register, bills counter machine, credit cards machine and lottery machine.
- Ensured that each customer receives outstanding service by providing a friendly environment.
- Regularly communicated with vendors and assisted with restocking shelving and product displays.
- Count money in cash drawer at the beginning of shift to ensure that amounts were correct and there was adequate change

## **TECHNICAL RECRUITER, APIDEL TECHNOLOGIES**

# FEBURARY 2017- JULY 2017 BERODA, GUJARAT, INDIA.

- ➤ Done recruiting for "Comcast" largest cable provider company in USA.
- > Depending on Job requirements provided by Comcast searched various job portals and found best candidates.
- Communicated with different candidates to check their experience through calls and scheduled their interviews.

## **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Gujarati
- > Hindi